<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on COVID Response Team - Richmond, Virginia</title>
    <link>http://www.covidresponseteamrva.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on COVID Response Team - Richmond, Virginia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.covidresponseteamrva.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Treatments</title>
      <link>http://www.covidresponseteamrva.com/services/treatments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.covidresponseteamrva.com/services/treatments/</guid>
      <description>We provide single, daily, weekly, and monthly treatments.
Electrostatic Disinfection One of our services harnesses electrostatic disinfection technology.
 Combative against COVID-19 Kills 99.99% of bacterial, viral, and fungal infections 4-10 minute process  Traditional Methods Discussed during consultation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.covidresponseteamrva.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.covidresponseteamrva.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Address: P.O. Box 42371 Richmond, VA 23242
Our hours of operation: We are available 24/7.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.covidresponseteamrva.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.covidresponseteamrva.com/about/</guid>
      <description>COVID Response Team, LLC was founded by two longtime Richmond, VA residents and entrepreneurs to combat virus outbreaks, in light of the COVID-19 outbreak. After seeing the devastating effects of COVID-19, it became apparent that better disinfection services will be needed not only to stop the COVID-19 spread, but also maintain future defenses against virsues, bacteria, and fungi to prevent this from ever happening again.
Mission Our mission is to provide exceptional disinfection services to ensure the health and safety of all our clients, in accordance with the latest public safety and health guidelines provided by the CDC.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>